I'm sitting in the quiet The storm has passed me
by She's holding me in, breathing And I don't
have to cry And in the peaceful laughter I hear
her ask my name I say it's complicated She says
mine's the same She asks me what I'm taking I wait
for her to laugh I tell her astrophysics That
cold and broken path My mother's silly
experiment The trap to make me fail The math I'll
never navigate The wind without a sail But she
just smiles and says, me too And my whole world
just stops The pieces of my broken life are
falling into slots She doesn't see a failure She
doesn't see a trap She's pointing to the
patterns on a different kind of map
She talks about the logic, the sanctuary from
the noise A place where all the chaos follows a
single voice She's speaking in my language, a
language I forgot She's not a part of Mother's
plan, she's something she could And she just
smiles and says, me too And my whole world just
stops The pieces of my broken life Are falling
into slots She doesn't see a failure She doesn't
see a trap She's pointing to the pattern Of the
same constellations on our map
The same constellations
She sees them too
Me too
you